Isaac Jones

Memphis, TN | (901) 608-0210 | ijones@perseverenow.org | www.linkedin.com/in/isaac-joness

SUMMARY

I work currently as a Teacher Assistant for Persevere, a non-profit teaching coding skills to those justice-impacted. I am also a User Experience Designer and working on a professional certificate in AI Engineering. And my goal is to develop the coding skills to ultimately become a software engineer.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Persevere Memphis, TN

Teaching Assistant

March 2021 - Present

- Assisted in helping students complete certifications using our curriculum freeCodeCamp.org in Responsive Web Design.
- Helped develop tests & quizzes for all curriculum from Responsive Web Design, JavaScript, and Data Structures & Algorithms, etc.
- Was responsible for organizing all material and creating Google classrooms & Slack channels for students in class.

Case Manager

October 2022 – January 2023

- Helped create documents for grant planning & learned how to use applications & programs such as Trello and Hubspot.
- Was tasked with creating spreadsheets and organizing different events surrounding fundraising and recruitment.

Mark H. Luttrell Transition Center

Memphis, TN

Residential Counselor Advisor

January 2020 – April 2021

- Assisted residents in making right choices and decisions while participating in the work release program at M.L.T.C.
- Maintained duties such as filing documents, cleaning common areas, restrooms, and sleeping quarters.

Cook II

September – December 2019

- Prepped, prepared meals for about three-hundred (300) residents at the main compound or facility for both breakfast and lunch.
- Maintained cleanliness of cooking areas at all times and even prepared for inspections, etc.

EDUCATION

Justice Through Code

New York,NY

Software Development Course

August 2023 -September 2023

- Took course called "Pathways to Tech '23" and learned the basics of Python 3.
- Learned about other things in free Coursera courses in Python 3 & using Generative AI.

Coursera *User Experience Design & AI Engineer*

Mountain View, CA

November 2022 – Present

• Completed User Experience Design Certificate, sponsored by Google.

- Took various courses for both UX Design and ChatGPT Data Analysis & Prompt Engineering.
- **Chattanooga State Technical Community College**

Chattanooga, TN

Undeclared

January 2001 – May 2002

- Maintained a 3.0 GPA while in attendance and was on the Dean's List
- Was awarded !A Who's Who Among Junior College Students" award

Lynwood High School

Lynwood, CA

High school diploma

March 1996 – June 1999

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Skills: Responsive Web Design, JavaScript, Data Structures & Algorithms, Front-End Libraries, Figma, Adobe XD

Interests: Reading, Long walks, Exercise.

Volunteering: volunteering at local food pantries.

Other Information: Completed software development and UX design courses on LinkedIn Learning and I am a Certified Peer Recovery Specialist and it is with the TN Department of Mental Health and Human Services